friendlyrentals.com 2018-02-24

# Friendly Rentals - Rent Apartments - Vacation Apartments For Days

FRIENDLY RENTALS, S.L. ensures the privacy of your personal data in accordance with Spanish Organic Act on Personal Data Protection 15/1999.

Visitors to this website are not obliged to provide any personal information. However, you may be asked to submit personal data if you choose to fill in a form.  

Any personal data thus submitted will be used to manage users’ requests and to send them information on our company and its services by any means of communication. By filling in a form on our website, you explicitly agree to receive such information. If you do not wish to receive this kind of information, you should send an email with the subject “UNSUBSCRIBE” to unsubscribe@friendlyrentals.com.  

Your personal data will be saved on a customer file owned and managed by FRIENDLY RENTALS, S.L., PASAJE SERT, 1-3 BAJOS, BARCELONA, 08003, CIF: B-63257810, entered in the Barcelona Companies Register at T 35922, F 1, S 8, H B 278180, I/A 1 (24.10.03).  

You may exercise your right to access, amend, cancel and oppose the use of your personal data by writing to the company at the above address, including a copy of your ID card, passport or equivalent document.  

If you do not provide your personal data, you will not be able to access the service in question. You have the right to receive an answer to any questions or queries you might have in this regard. If you submit your personal data in an email, the said email and the information it contains will be saved on a customer file in order to manage the request in question. You should be aware of your rights indicated in the previous paragraph.   

All your personal data will be removed from our database in the following circumstances:  

1\. At the user’s request.

2\. When this data is no longer of any use for the purpose for which it was submitted.

Should any questions or differences of opinion arise, both parties hereby expressly renounce their own jurisdiction or any other that may legally correspond to them and agree to submit themselves to the jurisdiction and authority of the courts of law of the city of the owner of website.
